<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fundraising on Value or Waste</title>
    <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/fundraising/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fundraising on Value or Waste</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/fundraising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Reasons NYC Startups Are Topping Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/109/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/109/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.inc.com/paul-grossinger/reasons-nyc-startups-top-sf-startups.html&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://images.inc.com/uploaded_files/image/1940x900/getty_181278609_82979.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;(Getty Images)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, I was seated at a café in Silicon Valley speaking to the founder of an early-stage enterprise software company, when we got to the nut of the conversation: he was raising money. The problem was: he was raising $4m at a $10m pre-money valuation, for a $14m post-money, for a company with eleven clients on pilot contracts paying under $2,000 per month, in several cases under $1,000 (&amp;hellip;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the valuation, and the estimation of potential scale, was so far out of whack with current market realities as to be grotesque, and it is this growing factor that makes New York and mid-Atlantic region companies increasingly superior investment opportunities to those in Silicon Valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.inc.com/paul-grossinger/reasons-nyc-startups-top-sf-startups.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Are Some of the VCs You Should Pitch When You Fundraise?</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/108/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/108/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mattermark.com/who-are-some-of-the-vcs-you-should-pitch-when-you-fundraise&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://wordpress.mattermark.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/pablo-5.png&#34; alt=&#34;(VCs and Fundraising)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have the resources to take your company to the next phase of product development and growth, your company is dead in the water. I’ve previously written about the seed fundraising process here, and the Series A fundraising process here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ancillary benefit of fundraising is that you learn a ton about your own business, your industry, your business model and the talent market by having conversations with great VCs. Entrepreneurs need to realize that fundraising isn’t JUST about you getting money for your business – it’s about you learning and gaining valuable intel that you can apply as you operate your company day-to-day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the years, I pitched hundreds of investors – individual angels and institutions – in the process of raising our seed, A and B rounds for Scripted.  Here is a list of some of the institutional investors that I learned the most from during the fundraising process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mattermark.com/who-are-some-of-the-vcs-you-should-pitch-when-you-fundraise&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>