<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth Hacks on Value or Waste</title>
    <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/growth-hacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth Hacks on Value or Waste</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/growth-hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Growth Hacks Any Small Business Can Implement</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/100/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/100/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.stfi.re/growth-hacks-small-businesses-can-implement&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/9-hacks-open-graph-620x350.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Growth Hacking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1996, an email company named Hotmail launched with a small group of users. By the end of 1997, that company had 12 million users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How did they grow so dramatically in just year and a half? Well, they looked at their initial numbers and saw that approximately 80 percent of new users came by referral from current users. To make the most of referrals, Hotmail created their iconic email postscript: “PS. I love you. Get your free email at Hotmail.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That single line, added at the end of every email sent through Hotmail, drove millions of new users in an ever-widening ripple effect.  Hotmail successfully created one of the first documented growth hacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growth hacking is the combination of product design, marketing, and data with the overall goal of driving customer growth.  Initially popular among fast-growing startups, the principles of growth hacking have since spread to the wider business world.  With a focus on understanding the customer and designing the right product, successful growth hacking drives growth in both the short- and long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how can you apply a growth hack like Hotmail’s to build your own business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.stfi.re/growth-hacks-small-businesses-can-implement&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>