<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup on Value or Waste</title>
    <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup on Value or Waste</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/110/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/110/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/ultimate-guide-startup-marketing&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/foundation.png&#34; alt=&#34;(Startup Marketing)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, startup marketing is a unique challenge often times because of the limited resources, whether it’s time, money or talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be sure every effort, no matter how small, is well-planned and flawlessly executed. And to make it even more difficult, the traditional marketing strategies don’t always work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Startup marketing is a whole different science. How so? The secret is properly combining the right channels: Content Marketing and PR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, starting from the beginning, here’s the complete Startup Marketing Manual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/ultimate-guide-startup-marketing&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Growth Hacks Any Small Business Can Implement</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/100/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/100/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.stfi.re/growth-hacks-small-businesses-can-implement&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/9-hacks-open-graph-620x350.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Growth Hacking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1996, an email company named Hotmail launched with a small group of users. By the end of 1997, that company had 12 million users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How did they grow so dramatically in just year and a half? Well, they looked at their initial numbers and saw that approximately 80 percent of new users came by referral from current users. To make the most of referrals, Hotmail created their iconic email postscript: “PS. I love you. Get your free email at Hotmail.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That single line, added at the end of every email sent through Hotmail, drove millions of new users in an ever-widening ripple effect.  Hotmail successfully created one of the first documented growth hacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growth hacking is the combination of product design, marketing, and data with the overall goal of driving customer growth.  Initially popular among fast-growing startups, the principles of growth hacking have since spread to the wider business world.  With a focus on understanding the customer and designing the right product, successful growth hacking drives growth in both the short- and long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how can you apply a growth hack like Hotmail’s to build your own business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.surepayroll.stfi.re/growth-hacks-small-businesses-can-implement&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does Venture Capital Drive the U.S. Economy?</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gsb.stanford.edu/insights/how-much-does-venture-capital-drive-us-economy&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.gsb.stanford.edu/sites/gsb/files/styles/1630x_variable/public/resources/ilya-vccapital-1015_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;(Photo Credit Reuters/Carlo Allegri)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past 30 years, venture capital has become a dominant force in the financing of innovative American companies. From Google to Intel to FedEx, companies supported by venture capital have profoundly changed the U.S. economy. Despite the young age of the venture capital industry, a fifth of current public U.S. companies received venture capital financing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, How much does it drive U.S. Economy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gsb.stanford.edu/insights/how-much-does-venture-capital-drive-us-economy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Value Stream Discovery: What to Test &amp; How to Measure</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/99/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/99/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.movestheneedle.com/value-stream-discovery-loop&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www-movestheneedle-com.zippykid.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/0211_overload-800x480.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;(photo credit associationnow.com)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great tools exist to track the current state of startup’s and enterprise innovation team’s business model assumptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ash Maurya’s Lean Canvas and Osterwalder’s Business Model Canvas come to mind. Tools/frameworks also exist to define and track experiments, such as Dave McClure’s Pirate Metrics, LSM’s Experiment board and our own Moves the Needle Experiment Map. Similar tools have been around for ages, by the way; used in lean manufacturing processes, Agile, kanban, scrum, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We appreciate the analog nature of these tools, because teams gather around the boards and discuss, brainstorm and share. The digital versions will come — well, they’re already here. I should say the digital versions may eventually become useful, but in the lean innovation world, we’re still pretty early and analog works better&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.movestheneedle.com/value-stream-discovery-loop&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>