<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Value or Waste</title>
    <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Value or Waste</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.valueorwaste.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>8 aha moments you need to have before Marketing your Startup</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/112/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/112/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ryangum.com/8-aha-moments-needed-before-marketing-your-startup&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ryangum.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/startup-channel-matrix.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;(Coelevate Matrix)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “If you build it, they will come” mindset doesn’t hold true in a world where attention spans are decreasing, alternatives are increasing, and up to $582 is spent on advertising to each person, every year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing your startup is hard, especially if you’re a solopreneur or a small team. If this is your first time around or are still early on in your startup journey you probably have some basic assumptions that you use to guide your marketing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But before you jump in, I’ve identified 8 ‘aha moments’, aka paradigm shifts, you need to have to maximize your efforts. I’ve focused on these specific points because they are common assumptions that can cost you wasted time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ryangum.com/8-aha-moments-needed-before-marketing-your-startup&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Startup Marketing</title>
      <link>http://www.valueorwaste.com/110/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.valueorwaste.com/110/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/ultimate-guide-startup-marketing&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/foundation.png&#34; alt=&#34;(Startup Marketing)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, startup marketing is a unique challenge often times because of the limited resources, whether it’s time, money or talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be sure every effort, no matter how small, is well-planned and flawlessly executed. And to make it even more difficult, the traditional marketing strategies don’t always work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Startup marketing is a whole different science. How so? The secret is properly combining the right channels: Content Marketing and PR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, starting from the beginning, here’s the complete Startup Marketing Manual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.kissmetrics.com/ultimate-guide-startup-marketing&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>